text: #01 WHEN I RETURNED HOME,
I'D BECOME A HERO
Goran: Did we do it?
Eric: Looks like the demons have retreated.
Goran: We didn't finish off the Demon King,
text: GORAN, THE WARRIOR
Goran: but we messed him up good.
text: ERIC, THE HERO
Eric: Yeah.
Eric: I doubt he'll try anything
else for a while.
Luck: If I could convert this into mana...
Eric: I guess all three of us
will make it home.
Goran: Guess so.
Luck: Or maybe that won't work unless
the rest of him dies too?
Eric: Luck?
Luck: Maybe if I amplify the
scant remnants... Or not?
Eric: Some things never change.
Goran: We drove off the Demon King,
and you're still fixated on that arm?
Luck: Huh?
Luck: Sorry, wasn't listening.
You say something?
Goran: This sort of thing's why you
can never get a girlfriend.
Goran: Well, it's time we said goodbye
to this gloomy dimensional rift.
Goran: That was one long battle.
Eric: It took even longer than I expected.
Eric: Too bad I had to miss out
on the birth of my child.
Goran: And I won't be surprised if my daughter's
forgotten what I look like.
Luck: The worries never end
when you have a family.
Luck: I'll just stay single.
Goran: Nah, Luck. Having a family
waiting for you is a wonderful thing.
Eric: That's right. Goran and I managed to keep
fighting because we have that support.
Eric: You better hurry up and
make a family of your own.
Goran: Man, you gotta be joking.
Eric: There are still that many demons?
Goran: Oh well. Time to go on a rampage.
Eric: Looks like I'll have to wait a
little longer to meet my kid.
Luck: We're already totally battle weary.
Luck: We'll never survive a head-on fight.
Luck: And so...
Luck: Eric, Goran.
Luck: Leave this to me, and get out of here!
Goran: What're you saying, Luck?!
Eric: You want us to leave you here,
and run for it?!
Luck: The Demon King hasn't been defeated yet.
Luck: Once he rises again, we're going
to need the hero's strength!
Goran: Then that doesn't concern me,
the warrior. I'll fight too!
Luck: Don't you have a family to go see?
Eric: Luck! Stop showing off!
Eric: Earth magic?
Goran: Luck!
Goran: Damn! He cast a barrier spell on it!
Goran: Quick screwing around, Luck!
Cancel this spell!
Eric: We can't leave you here alone!
Luck: You said your families are what's
supported you in battle.
Luck: To me, you guys are like family.
Eric: Luck...
Luck: I'll catch up soon enough.
Luck: You guys know how stubborn I can be.
Luck: Having you nearby will be too distracting
to fight all those demon enemies.
Luck: Please...
Luck: Go!
Eric: Luck!
Goran: Don't die on us!
Luck: Now come and get me, demons!
Luck: Don't think it'll be easy to get past me!
Luck: Let's do this!
Luck: The demons just won't stop coming.
Luck: I guess... this is my... limit.
Luck: That's when I suddenly
reached a turning point.
text: DEMON GENERAL
Luck: M-My energy...
Luck: My life force is... being absorbed?
Luck: It must be Drain Touch!
Luck: There went most of my mana, too.
Luck: Right back at you!
Luck: Drain Touch!
Luck: My Learning skill allows me to pick up
any spell that's used against me.
Luck: This'll let me recover and
replenish at the same time.
Luck: Bring it on!
Luck: I feel like now, I could fight for years!
Luck: How many weeks...
Luck: No, how many months have I been fighting?
Luck: I've lost track of time.
Luck: Whenever I got sleepy,
I'd self-cast a spell called Marionette.
Luck: By using that, my body would
keep fighting on while I slept.
Luck: I barely even felt like
I was human anymore.
Luck: Did I... kill them... all?
Luck: Recovered already, have you?
Luck: That was quick,
Luck: Demon King!
Luck: I thought it'd take you a decade.
Or at least several years.
Luck: I'll start by fighting in close,
and keep him from using his fiery magic!
Luck: Drain Touch!
Luck: This wound's more serious than I thought!
Luck: I'm in trouble if I don't recover soon!
Luck: I'd expect nothing less of
the Demon King's Hexblade.
Luck: Who needs a sword?! I'm a sorcerer!
Luck: Imprisoning Hellfire!
Luck: Drain Touch!
Luck: I knew it.
Luck: You're too busy defending
against Imprisoning Hellfire
Luck: to do anything about Drain Touch!
Luck: Time to choose!
Luck: Will Imprisoning Hellfire
burn you to a crisp,
Luck: or will you lose all your life force?!
Luck: Did... I do it?
Luck: Oh, yeah!
Luck: Now then, where am I?
Luck: Well, following that road
will take me somewhere.
Luck: Great. I'm broke, and my
adventurer card burned up.
Luck: This is the royal capital... isn't it?
guard 1: H-Hey, stop right there!
Luck: What's the matter?
Luck: They even gave me clothes.
Luck: Talk about nice guys.
Luck: Well, I'll start by dropping
by Goran's place.
Luck: I-It's huge!
Butler: May I help you?
Luck: Um...
Luck: I'd like to see Goran.
Butler: Do you have an appointment?
Luck: No, I'm afraid I don't.
Butler: I cannot allow you in, if you lack one.
Luck: If you tell him Luck is here,
he'll understand.
Butler: We get your kind here quite often.
Luck: I'm telling the truth!
Butler: Please take your leave.
Luck: Phooey.
Luck: Whatever.
Luck: Next, I'll go to the guild,
and get my adventurer card reissued.
Luck: That stone statue didn't
used to be there.
Luck: He's a sorcerer, huh?
Luck: And a handsome one, at that.
Luck: Excuse me.
passerby 1: Huh?
Luck: Who is this a statue of?
passerby 1: What?! You don't know?!
Luck: Sorry, no.
passerby 1: No wonder.
passerby 1: Looks like you just arrived
from the boonies.
passerby 1: I guess it's no surprise you don't know.
Luck: Okay?
passerby 1: It's a statue of the Great Saint Luck!
Luck: Saint... Luck?
passerby 1: A great hero who, ten years ago,
passerby 1: held off a horde of demons
by himself inside a dimensional rift!
Luck: That's... me?!
passerby 1: His efforts saved the entire world!
passerby 1: Saint Luck, a great hero
and a great sage!
Luck: I bet this means they think
I died ten years ago.
Luck: Ten years ago?!
Luck: I was fighting for an entire decade?
text: ADVENTURERS GUILD HEADQUARTERS
adventurer 1: Haven't seen you around before.
Luck: Excuse me.
adventurer 1: Don't ignore me!
adventurer 1: You need to learn
how things work around—
Luck: Goran!
Goran: I'm so happy you came back alive!
Luck: Are you crying? And are you old?
Goran: I'm not cryin'! I have aged!
Goran: We're talking a decade!
Ten years have passed!
Luck: He's bawling.
Luck: These taste good!
Luck: They're so yummy!
Luck: Y'know, I haven't eaten
anything in ten years!
Luck: I got all the energy I needed using Drain
Touch, but my stomach's been empty!
Luck: What's the big idea?!
Goran: Don't overdo it on solid food
after a long fast.
Goran: Let's get you some rice gruel.
Goran: Hey! Bring some rice gruel!
Goran: On the double!
Goran: Still, I'm surprised
you survived that mess.
Luck: Managing to learn Drain Touch
made a big difference.
Eric: I've brought the rice gruel.
Goran: Enter!
Goran: Oh, you're finally here.
Eric: You're looking well, Luck.
Luck: Eric?
Eric: It's... It's good to have you back!
Luck: You too, huh?
Luck: What am I supposed to do with
two crying middle-aged guys?
Luck: Looks like even sexy guys have to age.
Eric: Speaking of, Luck. Isn't this unnatural?
Luck: Isn't what?
Goran: Yeah, you haven't aged at all.
Goran: In fact, I could swear you got younger.
Luck: Don't be ridiculous. That's not...
Luck: I got younger!
Luck: What's going on?!
Luck: When I defeated the
Demon King with Drain Touch,
Luck: I absorbed a bunch of his life force.
Luck: Maybe that's what did it.
Luck: What's wrong?
Goran: You defeated the Demon King?!
Luck: Y-Yeah. He revived and showed up again.
Eric: Luck, the kingdom has been
beefing up its military
Eric: in anticipation of the
Demon King's recovery and invasion.
Eric: But if you've already defeated him...
then we owe you some reward.
Goran: You said it, Your Majesty.
Luck: "Your Majesty"?
Luck: You're the king?!
Luck: I mean, I knew you were royalty!
Eric: The previous king felt I deserved it,
for driving back the Demon King.
Goran: Eric is now the king.
Goran: And I'm Grand Master of
the Adventurers Guild.
Luck: You two have really done
well for yourselves.
Goran: Well, you're now a savior
and a great sage.
Goran: The supreme sorcerer,
Archduke Luck Franzen.
Luck: Too long!
Luck: And what's with the "archduke"?!
I'm not nobility!
Luck: Who's Franzen?!
Eric: I wanted to reward your service,
so I gave you a noble title.
Goran: It was the first thing he did
after that statue was built.
Luck: Oh yeah, the statue!
What's the story with that?
Goran: Oh, you saw it? Lookin' good, isn't he?
Luck: Way better than I look.
Eric: Well, the sculptor had never met you.
Eric: He made it based on my words and Goran's,
and that's how it turned out.
Luck: I knew these two were behind it.
Luck: Still, I'm surprised the peerage didn't
pitch a fit when you made me one of them.
Luck: You had no family, and it
was believed you were dead.
Luck: Doesn't that mean it's going to be a
problem now that I've come back alive?
Luck: Well, let's not change
the official story that Luck is dead.
Goran: Luck...
Eric: Then, what will you do now?
Luck: It's a good opportunity.
Luck: I'll start over from square one
as an adventurer.
Luck: Wow.
Goran: There's your new adventurer card.
Goran: We used an info-masking spell
so that only the name "Lock" appears.
Luck: Where did "Lock" come from?
Goran: Your real name is Luck Lock Franzen.
Luck: They even gave me a middle name?
Goran: Your first job of
"S-Rank Supreme Sorcerer" is hidden,
Goran: so only your second job of
"F-Rank Warrior" shows up.
Goran: From now on, you'll be known
as Lock, the F-rank warrior.
Luck: Sorry to make you do all this.
Goran: Sure, but won't you get bored
starting over from square one?
Goran: You could fight stronger enemies.
Goran: I've already fought plenty
of strong enemies.
Butler: Saint Lu... Master Lock.
Butler: I was terribly rude to you the other day.
Lock: That's okay. I mean,
I wasn't very presentable.
Butler: You are too kind.
Butler: Where are you headed?
Lock: To the Adventurers Guild.
Butler: Until later, then.
Arone: Hello. I am Arone, the receptionist.
Lock: I'd like to do this.
Arone: All right.
Arone: Goblin extermination.
Arone: By yourself?
Lock: Yes, that's the plan.
Arone: It's dangerous for a rookie to
solo a goblin-extermination job.
Arone: I cannot recommend it.
Lock: I know, but I'll be fine.
Lock: I'm really S-rank anyway.
Arone: It's not uncommon for rookies to die
because they underestimate goblins.
Lock: Right...
Arone: I cannot recommend going solo.
Ario: Would you like to come with us?
Ario: We're F-rank adventurers too.
Ario: A mage and a bow scout.
Ario: We could use someone on the front line.
Ginny: You're a warrior, right?
Arone: A wonderful idea!
Arone: You three will exterminate goblins!
Approved!
Lock: Huh? But I never said I'd—
Arone: It is a wonderful idea!
Lock: Yes, ma'am.
Lock: Well...
Lock: It's important to train rookies, too.
Ario: Well met. My name's Ario.
Ario: I can use Fireball.
Ario: This is my younger sister Ginny.
Ario: Ginny here. I have our
archery needs covered.
Lock: I'm Lock. I use a sword.
Nice to meet you.
Ginny: Losses include two months' worth of
stored crops, two cows, and three sheep.
Ginny: The western fencing often gets damaged,
so they probably come from that direction.
Ario: So, based on goblin habitat ranges,
the den is...
Ginny: The evidence suggests there
are about ten of them.
Ario: Yeah, thereabouts.
Ginny: This way. I don't think
it's far from here.
Ario: Okay, let's go.
Lock: Ginny is quite a skilled scout.
Lock: She sticks to the hunt,
and she's quick-witted.
Lock: She doesn't seem like an F-rank to me.
Lock: But...
Lock: They've misjudged how
many goblins there are.
Lock: They haven't noticed
the camouflaged footprints.
Lock: And it's important to note,
Lock: goblins aren't clever enough
to hide their footprints.
Lock: In other words, there's some
other monster leading them.
Lock: Ginny.
Ginny: What's up?
Lock: Nah, never mind.
Ario: What's the holdup, you two?
Ginny: Okay!
Ginny: Let's go, Lock.
Lock: You don't train someone by
telling them everything in advance.
Lock: There's a lot you can learn from failure.
Lock: Especially while you're young.
Lock: But now that I've chosen not to tell them,
the responsibility is mine.
Lock: I swear I won't let these two die.
Ginny: That must be the den.
Ario: Looks like an old mine shaft.
Lock: This looks bad.
Ginny: It does?
Ario: I don't think so.
Ario: Goblins are nocturnal.
We should attack while it's still daytime.
Lock: I'll take the lead.
Lock: Ginny, give me covering fire.
Lock: Once we're in there, guard our rear.
Ginny: Will do.
Lock: Ario, conserve your magic
as much as possible as we go.
Ario: All right.
Lock: Let's go!
Ario: We've already defeated
over thirty of them.
Ginny: Isn't that more than we expected?
Lock: Packs like this are often
led by a hobgoblin.
Lock: Ario, can you still launch Fireball?
Ario: If I push really hard.
But I'm nearly spent.
Lock: Ginny, you have enough arrows?
Ginny: I only have three left.
Ario: Let's withdraw.
Ginny: But!
Ario: It's dangerous to push on ahead when
we're low on magic and arrows.
Lock: Good decision.
Ginny: Okay, fine.
Lock: A goblin lord.
Lock: It's strange.
Lock: The way they steal livestock
a little at a time
Lock: means the one in charge is giving
systematic orders to the goblins.
Lock: That suggests a certain
level of intelligence.
Lock: But I don't sense that at all
from that goblin lord.
Lock: There must be something else
calling the shots after all.
Sia: Pipsqueak!
Sia: Stay out of my way!
Sia: Or else!
Credits: TRANSLATION: DUANE JOHNSON
Credits: TIMING: EDGAR CRUZ
EDITING: ZACHARY CARLYSLE
Credits: QUALITY CONTROL: GABRIELLA ALABANZA
TRANSLATION CHECK: SRIRAM GURUNATHAN
text (top): NEXT TIME: THERE WAS A FORMIDABLE FOE
DEEP INSIDE THE DEN